seeqpod.com 2009-04-03

# SeeqPod Playable Search - Find. Discover. Watch. Listen. Share. | Privacy Policy

NOTICE: [Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec01.shtm) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission. 

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how SeeqPod treats personal information that SeeqPod collects and receives, including information related to your past use of SeeqPod products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SeeqPod does not own or control, or to people that SeeqPod does not employ or manage.

## Information Collection and Use

### General

  * SeeqPod collects personal information when you register with SeeqPod, when you use SeeqPod products or services, when you visit SeeqPod pages or the pages of certain SeeqPod partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. SeeqPod may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with SeeqPod and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * SeeqPod automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, SeeqPod cookie information, and the page you request.
  * SeeqPod uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * SeeqPod does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, and with your express permission, may or may not share this information under the following possible circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with SeeqPod under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help SeeqPod communicate with you about offers from SeeqPod and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of SeeqPod's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if SeeqPod is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, SeeqPod will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
    * SeeqPod displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.
    * SeeqPod does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

## Cookies

  * SeeqPod may set and access SeeqPod cookies on your computer. 
  * SeeqPod lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to SeeqPod's cookies. 

## Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

### General

  * You can edit your SeeqPod Account Information, at any time.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the SeeqPod service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the SeeqPod Newsletter, that are considered part of your SeeqPod account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your SeeqPod account by visiting our Account Deletion page.

## Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
  * To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please contact us anytime.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * SeeqPod may update this policy, from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your SeeqPod account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## Questions and Suggestions 

  * If you have questions or suggestions contact us at:   
SeeqPod Inc.  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
6475 Christie Avenue Suite 475  
Emeryville, CA 94608  
(510) 597-1234  

Effective June 17, 2008
